Stanislav Bulovskii

SUMMARY

I am a software developer with 11 years of experience on .Net specializing in backend including 7 years of experience in FinTech. I start to be interested in GoLang, i have experience with golang(half a year) and i want to change .net to golang. I'm also open to learning about neural networks, AI and Machine learning

EXPERIENCE

Ozon Technologies - the second largest marketplace in Russia. 🖸

Remote / St. Petersburg, Russia

Backend developer of WMS - Warehouse Management System

02.2021 - 07.2024

Net Core Go postgreSQL kafka gRPC ASP.Net Core NUnit gitlab Distributed Systems Microservices

- WMS is built using microservice architecture, deployed by gitlab in k8s and docker. Our product is a high-load system, already delivered to our customers, and work 24/7.
- I've increased the performance of the Item service by splitting it in two, scaling horizontally, and getting rid of the database binding. The RPS of the service before the split was 1200 on average and 5400 at the maximum. The RPS for both services after the split is a combined 1720 on average and 11300 maximum
- I have fixed all internal errors of the Topology service by adding and modifying existing indexes in the database. The number of 500th errors is zero
- o I increased the stability (including latency and error rate) of the topology-flow service from 98.79 to 99.90 % by adding new and modifying existing indexes in the database and distributing the load on the database. After that, stability moved to the green zone (more than 99.50 %)
- o I increased the speed of endpoint get-tags by 100 times (from 700ms to 7ms) by denormalizing the data in the database

ETNA Software - trading and exchange software development 🖸

St. Petersburg, Russia

03.2015 - 05.2019

Backend developer

C# MS SQL

- I was responsible for the development and support of Etna Trader. Etna Trader is an exchange trading platform designed
 for traders who want to buy or sell stocks, options or other derivatives on exchanges such as NYSE, NASDAQ or AMEX.
 Our product is a web-based, distributed, multi-component, multi-trading system and is already in use by our customers
- I developed and maintained two components of our system Security Collector, which is designed to store and update a list of securities (stocks, options, etc.) in a database and TimeSeriesHistoryFiller, which is designed to collect and store stock trading candles (historical data) in a database

Bank "Saint-Petersburg" - one of the top 15 banks in Russia ♂

St. Petersburg, Russia

05.2011 - 03.2015

• Software developer for algo systems and trading robots

C# WPF StockSharp MS SQL

- I created and put into operation a trading robot for trading securities on the stock exchange.
- I created and put into operation a module for analyzing historical and imputed volatility created and put into operation a log converter for stock exchange orders from the format of one exchange (MICEX) to the format of another exchange (FORTS).
- I created and put into operation a program for searching "iceberg" orders

SKILLS

Languages: C#, .Net, golang, C/C++
Databases & ORM: PostgreSQL, MS-SQL, Dapper

Technologies: gRPC, protobuf, Rest, .Net Core, .NET Framework, ASP.NetCore, kafka, LINQ, DI, WPF, StockSharp

Testing: NUnit, xUnit, Fluent Assertions, Moq. Bogus

CI/CI: GitLab pipelines, k8s, Grafana, GrayLog, Jaeger, Octopus Deploy

Tools: git, Docker, Rider, DataGrip, Visual Studio, NuGet, Confluence, TFS, Ankhsvn, TortoiseSVN, RedMine

Foreign languages: English - B1

EDUCATION

• MSc-equivalent (300 credits) in Applied Mathematics and Computer Science

St. Petersburg State University

Faculty of Applied Mathematics and Control Processes

Professional Development, Courses

- Databases, PostgreSQL QPT: Query Optimization
- .Net CLRium #6: Concurrency & Parallelism